export const golferQuizQuestions = [
  {
    question: 'Who won The Masters in 2023?',
    options: ['Tiger Woods', 'Rory McIlroy', 'Jon Rahm', 'Patrick Cantlay'],
    correctAnswer: 'Jon Rahm',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of these golfers has won a major in their career?',
    options: ['Justin Thomas', 'Max Homa', 'Sahith Theegala', 'Tony Finau'],
    correctAnswer: 'Justin Thomas',
  },
  {
    question: 'How many career major championship does Tiger Woods have?',
    options: ['3', '8', '15', '18'],
    correctAnswer: '15',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which American golfer has won an Olympic Gold Medal?',
    options: [
      'Jordan Spieth',
      'Tiger Woods',
      'Xander Schauffele',
      'Justin Thomas',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Xander Schauffele',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which popular golfer has 4 career major championships, but none since 2014?',
    options: ['Rory McIlroy', 'Jon Rahm', 'Tony Finau', 'Jason Day'],
    correctAnswer: 'Rory McIlroy',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Who won his fifth career major championship in 2023, which was also his third PGA Championship?',
    options: ['Rory McIlroy', 'Brooks Koepka', 'Collin Morikawa', 'Max Homa'],
    correctAnswer: 'Brooks Koepka',
  },
  {
    question: 'Who is known for wearing his trademarked orange on Sundays?',
    options: ['Tiger Woods', 'Jon Rahm', 'Scottie Scheffler', 'Rickie Fowler'],
    correctAnswer: 'Rickie Fowler',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Who won the 2022 Masters? Hint: He also has unorthodox footwork. ',
    options: [
      'Scottie Scheffler',
      'Xander Schauffele',
      'Jon Rahm',
      'Patrick Cantlay',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Scottie Scheffler',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Name the Norwegian golfer who learned English from watching historical films.',
    options: ['Matt Fitzpatrick', 'Viktor Hovland', 'Jason Day', 'Tony Finau'],
    correctAnswer: 'Viktor Hovland',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which golfer has risen in popularity through his social media presence, hosting a podcast called "Get A Grip"?',
    options: ['Max Homa', 'Jon Rahm', 'Scottie Scheffler', 'Rory McIlroy'],
    correctAnswer: 'Max Homa',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Who keeps detailed records of every shot he has played in competition, and won the 2022 U.S. Open?',
    options: [
      'Justin Thomas',
      'Jason Day',
      'Matt Fitzpatrick',
      'Jordan Spieth',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Matt Fitzpatrick',
  },
  {
    question: 'Who is known as "Patty Ice"?',
    options: [
      'Rory McIlroy',
      'Matt Fitzpatrick',
      'Patrick Cantlay',
      'Max Homa',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Patrick Cantlay',
  },
];

export const tournamentQuizQuestions = [
  {
    question: 'How many majors are played each year?',
    options: ['1', '3', '4', '5'],
    correctAnswer: '4',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which major is played at the same course each year?',
    options: [
      'The U.S. Open',
      'The Masters',
      'PGA Championship',
      'All of the above',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'The Masters',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which tournament is considered the "Toughest Test in Golf"?',
    options: [
      'The Masters',
      'PGA Championship',
      'The U.S. Open',
      'The Open Championship',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'The U.S. Open',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which major is the oldest?',
    options: [
      'The Masters',
      'The Open Championship',
      'PGA Championship',
      'The PLAYERS Championship',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'The Open Championship',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which event is a team competition?',
    options: [
      'The Masters',
      'The Ryder Cup',
      'PGA Championship',
      'The PLAYERS Championship',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'The Ryder Cup',
  },
  {
    question: 'How many players are on each side in The Ryder Cup?',
    options: ['4', '8', '10', '12'],
    correctAnswer: '12',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which teams compete against each other in The Ryder Cup?',
    options: [
      'North America vs Europe',
      'USA vs England',
      'USA vs The World',
      'USA vs Europe',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'USA vs Europe',
  },
  {
    question: 'How many players are there in most major tournaments?',
    options: ['100', '125', '156', '200'],
    correctAnswer: '156',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which organization runs The Open Championship?',
    options: ['PGA Tour', 'The R&A', 'The USGA', 'None of those'],
    correctAnswer: 'The R&A',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which month is The Masters typically held?',
    options: ['March', 'April', 'June', 'July'],
    correctAnswer: 'April',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which tournament is always played at TPC Sawgrass, famous for their island green on the 17th hole?',
    options: [
      'US Open',
      'The Masters',
      'PGA Championship',
      'The PLAYERS Championship',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'The PLAYERS Championship',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which month is The U.S. Open typically held?',
    options: ['April', 'May', 'June', 'July'],
    correctAnswer: 'June',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which major championship invites club professionals?',
    options: [
      'The Masters',
      'The U.S. Open',
      'PGA Championship',
      'No tournaments allow this',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'PGA Championship',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which major championship features "links" golf?',
    options: [
      'The Open Championship',
      'The U.S. Open',
      'PGA Championship',
      'The PLAYERS Championship',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'The Open Championship',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which organization runs The U.S. Open?',
    options: ['PGA Tour', 'USGA', 'The R&A', 'None of those'],
    correctAnswer: 'USGA',
  },
];

export const basicsQuizQuestions = [
  {
    question: 'What does "par" mean?',
    options: [
      'Your total score for the round',
      'Your average score over all of your rounds played',
      'A standard used in golf that indicates the number of strokes an expert golfer is expected to take to complete a hole or a round',
      'Completing a hole without ever going into a hazard',
    ],
    correctAnswer:
      'A standard used in golf that indicates the number of strokes an expert golfer is expected to take to complete a hole or a round',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is a "birdie"?',
    options: [
      'Completing a hole one stroke under par',
      'Finishing your round one stroke under par',
      'Completing a hole one stroke over par',
      'Finishing your round with a better score than you anticipated',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Completing a hole one stroke under par',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is a "bogey"?',
    options: [
      'Completing a hole one stroke under par',
      'Finishing your round one stroke over par',
      'Completing a hole after hitting the tee shot into the rough',
      'Completing a hole one stroke over par',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Completing a hole one stroke over par',
  },
  {
    question: `When should you arrive at the course when playing a round of golf?`,
    options: [
      'At your tee time',
      'At least 30 minutes prior to your tee time in order to check-in and warm-up first',
    ],
    correctAnswer:
      'At least 30 minutes prior to your tee time in order to check-in and warm-up first',
  },
  {
    question: `After hitting the ball, what should you do if you've created a divot?`,
    options: [
      `Nothing, because nature will take care of it and it'll grow back eventually`,
      'Repair the divot',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Repair the divot',
  },
  {
    question: `What is the name of the person that assists golfers during their round by carrying their bag and providing advice?`,
    options: ['Butler', 'Concierge', 'Caddie', 'Groundskeeper'],
    correctAnswer: 'Caddie',
  },
  {
    question: `Are you allowed to mark your ball then lift, clean, and replace it on the green?`,
    options: ['Yes', 'No, play it as it lies'],
    correctAnswer: 'Yes',
  },
  {
    question: `If you're in a sand trap, what should you do?`,
    options: [
      `Rake the sand after hitting your shot so that it's restored to good condition for other golfers`,
      'Pick up the ball, give yourself a penalty stroke, and drop the ball in nearby grass',
    ],
    correctAnswer: `Rake the sand after hitting your shot so that it's restored to good condition for other golfers`,
  },
  {
    question:
      'You may improve your lie without penalty if your ball is in the rough',
    options: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'False',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the fringe?',
    options: [
      'The edge of a penalty area',
      'The area surrounding the putting green and serves as a transition zone between the green and the fairway or rough',
      'Out of bounds',
      'Where golfers tee off to start the hole',
    ],
    correctAnswer:
      'The area surrounding the putting green and serves as a transition zone between the green and the fairway or rough',
  },
  {
    question:
      'What unit of measurement is used for the distance of a golf hole from tee to green?',
    options: ['Feet', 'Yards', 'Clublengths'],
    correctAnswer: 'Yards',
  },
  {
    question:
      'How is it typically determined who is next to play after teeing off?',
    options: [
      'The first person who hit their tee shot',
      'The person closest to the hole.',
      'The person farthest from the hole',
      'The last person to hit their tee shot',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'The person farthest from the hole',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which golf club is typically used to hit the ball as far as possible?',
    options: ['Putter', 'Wedge', 'Iron', 'Driver'],
    correctAnswer: 'Driver',
  },
];
